http://www.dianeromanello.com/home/privacy_policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
At Bentley Global Arts Group, we recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers and visitors and have established this privacy policy as a demonstration of our firm commitment to privacy. Below we describe why we gather customer and visitor information, what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we use the information for.
Summation
Information and data collected by Bentley Global Arts Group is used exclusively for order fulfillment, in-house research, and our own site development and marketing efforts. No data or personal information will be sold or traded to any third party for any reason. Ever.
Payment Information
All payment data (credit card number, expiration, etc) is encrypted and stored temporarily to enable the transaction to be processed.
Limited information is stored long term, allowing us to edit or credit the account being used in the transaction.
The only data stored long term are the the last four digits of the credit card used as well as the transaction ID.
Personal Information
When you order from our web site, we collect the following information: your name, address, email, and telephone number.
This information is used exclusively for processing your order and is routinely purged from servers and archived on secure servers within our corporate offices.
How we use "cookies"
A "cookie" is a small file stored on your computer by a web site which gives you a numeric user ID and stores certain information about your activity on the site. We use cookies to store information on your product selections and search queries as you shop on our site, but we do not store any personal information or financial information about you using cookies.We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of this site, such as the shopping basket and site search, will not function properly.
Data Sharing
We do not sell, share, trade or distribute any personal information relating to you and your order history to third parties for ANY reason.Furthermore, you may opt to remove your name and contact information from our own internal promotional lists by following the details included with the promotional material, e-mail, etc.
Your Security
Bentley Global Arts Group employs security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our web site encrypts your credit card number prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology.
Disclaimer
INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS CONTAINED IN THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, AND LINKS, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITH NO WARRANTY. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, BENTLEY GLOBAL ARTS GROUP DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO SUCH INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NONINFRINGEMENT, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS, AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR COURSE OF PERFORMANCE. IN ADDITION, THE GLOBAL ARTS GROUP DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA THIS SITE IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT. BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY.PRICE AND AVAILABILITY INFORMATION IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE.
Limitation of Liability
SITE CONTENT IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, BENTLEY GLOBAL ARTS GROUP, LLC DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.BENTLEY GLOBAL ARTS GROUP, LLC WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY THAT ACCOMPANY OR RESULT FROM YOUR USE OF ITS SITE. THESE INCLUDE (BUT ARE NOT LIMITED TO) DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY USE OF (OR INABILITY TO USE) THE SITES OR ANY SITE TO WHICH YOU HYPERLINK FROM OUR SITES, FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE FAILURE.ALSO, WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING DAMAGES INTENDED TO COMPENSATE SOMEONE DIRECTLY FOR A LOSS OR INJURY, DAMAGES REASONABLY EXPECTED TO RESULT FROM A LOSS OR INJURY (LEGALLY, "CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES"), OR OTHER MISCELLANEOUS DAMAGES AND EXPENSES RESULTING DIRECTLY FROM A LOSS OR INJURY (LEGALLY, "INCIDENTAL DAMAGES").FURTHERMORE, WE ARE NOT LIABLE EVEN IF WE'VE BEEN NEGLIGENT OR IF OUR AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.EXCEPTION: IN CERTAIN STATES THE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW US TO LIMIT OR EXCLUDE LIABILITY FOR THESE "INCIDENTAL" OR "CONSEQUENTIAL" DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY. BUT IN ANY EVENT, OUR LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL LOSSES, DAMAGES, INJURIES, AND CLAIMS OF EVERY KIND (CLAIMED UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY) WILL NOT BE GREATER THAN THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO ACCESS OUR SITE.
Jurisdiction
Unless otherwise specified, the materials on this site are presented to provide information about Bentley Global Arts Group, LLC and its products.Bentley Global Arts Group, LLC controls and operates this
Web site from its headquarters in Austin, Texas, in the United States of America. We in no way imply that the materials on the site is appropriate or available for use outside of the United States. If you use our site from locations outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. In addition, you may not use or export the materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations.These terms and conditions, and the agreement they create, shall be governed by and interpreted according to the laws of the State of Texas (without applying the state's conflict-of-law principles). Bentley Global Arts Group, LLC reserves the right to bring any civil action in Texas, arising from your violation of the terms and conditions of this agreement.
Changes
Bentley Global Arts Group, LLC reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update these policies, and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, or updates.
Last Updated: January 16, 2013
FIND ART
Best Sellers
Boats | Sailing
Sunset | Sunrise
Ponds
Beaches
Tropical
Diane- Bob G.
Copyright © 2020 Diane Romanello. All Rights Reserved. | Terms of Service | Privacy Policy
